Say hello to his little friend.
Bad Johnson is a comedy, fantasy, romance film directed by Huck Botko.
With women practically throwing themselves at him, Rich can’t control himself.
But he continually blames his penis, which seems to have a mind of its own.
After ruining yet another promising relationship with Jamie, Rich has finally
had enough and wishes his penis would just leave him alone.
The next morning, Rich wakes up to find his wish has come
true and his johnson is no longer on his body.
Rich Johnson, played by Cam Gigandet.
Rich's Penis, played by Nick Thune.
Lindsay Young, played by Katherine Cunningham.
Josh Nelson, played by Kevin Miller.
Emily, played by Jessica Joy.
Samantha, played by Katie Rich.
Bad Johnson, known as Schlong Story in some markets, is a 2014
American sex comedy film directed by Huck Botko.
The film explores themes of cheating, womanizer,
gym, personal trainer, urologist.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.